Guide to the New York State Agricultural Society records, 1841-1990.
New York State Agricultural Society records, 1841-1990.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State Agricultural Society records, 1841-1990, 1932-1990 (bulk).
1759
New York State Agricultural Society.
14.2 cubic ft.
Correspondence, citations and resolutions, speeches, membership lists, a catalog, and proceedings and minutes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records include correspondence, citations and resolutions, speeches, membership lists, an 1859 catalog from the Society's museum, and printed and mimeographed copies of proceedings and minutes of annual meetings. Includes correspondence of Charles H. Baldwin, Perley M. Eastman, Joseph M. Hurley, and Van C. Whittemore.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records include correspondence, citations and resolutions, speeches, membership lists, an 1859 catalog from the Society's museum, and printed and mimeographed copies of proceedings and minutes of annual meetings. Includes correspondence of Charles H. Baldwin, Perley M. Eastman, Joseph M. Hurley, and Van C. Whittemore.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State Agricultural Society.; Baldwin, Charles H.; Eastman, Perley M.; Hurley, Joseph M.; Whittemore, Van C.
Subjects:
Agricultural museums--New York (State); Agriculture--New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- 1932 and earlier (Box 1)
- 1938-1946 (Box 2)
- 1947-1952 (Box 3)
- 1944-1945 (Box 4)
- 1951-1952 (Box 5)
- 1952 (cont.) (Box 6)
- 1953 (Box 7)
- Membership list, 1933-1934 (Box 8)
- Programs, 1933-1934 (Box 8)
- Ag Society receipts, 1933 (Box 8)
- Financial records, 1929-1939 (Box 8)
- Membership booklets, 1931 (Box 8)
- Accounts, 1953 (Box 8)
- Ag Society dinners, 1935 (Box 8)
- Membership, 1953 (Box 8)
- Accts and membership, 1951 (Box 8)
- Treasurer and financial reports, 1948 (Box 8)
- Accounts, 1952 (Box 8)
- Membership and treasurers report, 1952 (Box 8)
- Story of the Agricultural Society, 1951 (Box 8)
- Reports of treasurer, 1951 (Box 8)
- Membership, 1950 (Box 8)
- Annual dues, 1951 (Box 8)
- Reservations and dinner, 1950 (Box 8)
- Programs, membership, and financial reports, 1949 (Box 8)
- Records, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
- Treasurers report, 1941 (Box 9)
- Financial report, 1943 (Box 9)
- Treasurers report, 1944 (Box 9)
- Treasurers report, 1946 (Box 9)
- Financial report, 1940 (Box 9)
- Treasurers report, 1938 (Box 9)
- Treasurers report, 1936 (Box 9)
- Financial report, 1938 (Box 9)
- Treasurers report, 1937 (Box 9)
- Treasurers report, 1947 (Box 9)
- Accounting report, 1938 (Box 9)
- Ag Society 100 anniversary booklet, 1932 (Box 9)
- Pictures 100th anniversary Ag Society (Box 9)
- Century Farm citations, 1948-1950 (Box 9)
- Various programs and citations & membership, 19 (Box 9)
- Spiral notebook - membership, 1956-1966 (Box 9)
- Financial reports, 1963-1969 (Box 9)
- Tom McMillan fund, 19 (Box 9)
- Misc. pictures, 19 (Box 9)
- Dinner pictures, 1953-1954 (Box 9)
- Misc. correspondence, 19 (Box 9)
- Financial records, 1960 (Box 9)
- Financial records, 1970 (Box 9)
- Century Farm awards, 1975 (Box 9)
- Financial reports, 1962 (Box 9)
- Various Century Farm awards, 19 (Box 9)
- Various Ag Society citations, 19 (Box 9)
- Various newspaper clippings, 1957 (Box 10)
- Newspaper clippings, 1959 (Box 10)
- Newspaper clippings, 1953 (Box 10)
- Newspaper clippings, 1955 (Box 10)
- Newspaper clippings, 1969 (Box 10)
- Newspaper clippings, 1958 (Box 10)
- Newspaper clippings, 1986 (Box 10)
- Ag Society records, 1955-1956 (Box 10)
- Centennial medalion, 19 (Box 10)
- Dinner meeting information, 1932 (Box 10)
- Dinner meeting information, 1942 (Box 10)
- Dinner meeting information, 1946 (Box 10)
- Dinner meeting information, 1948-1973 (Box 10)
- Dinner meeting, 1974 (Box 11)
- Financial records, 1971-1974 (Box 11)
- Thomas Milliman file, 19 (Box 11)
- IRS files, 1963-1973 (Box 11)
- Ag Society meeting, 1974 (Box 11)
- "Some Opportunities" report, 1963 (Box 11)
- Ag Society meeting, 1947 (Box 11)
- Ag Society correspondence, 1949-1953 (Box 11)
- Ag Society correspondence, 1955-1962 (Box 11)
- Ag Society correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 12)
- Ag Society dinner correspondence, 1963-1973 (Box 12)
- Ag Society by-laws, article of incorporation & amendments, 19 (Box 12)
- Press release - Century Farm awards, 1974 (Box 12)
- Pamphlets on awards, 19 (Box 12)
- Ag Society records, 1965-1974 (Box 13)
- Ag Society records, 1975-1978 (Box 14)
- Misc. correspondence, 19 (Box 14)
- Historical facts, clippings & photos, 19 (Box 14)
- Bicentennial Farms, 1976 (Box 14)
- Summer meeting, 1965 (Box 14)
- Century Farm listings, 19 (Box 14)
- Ag Society records, 1979-1983 (Box 15)
- Ag Society records, 1984-1986 (Box 16)
- Summer meeting, 1980 (Box 16)
- Summer meeting, 1979 (Box 16)
- Ag Society records, 1980 (Box 16)
- Century Farm booklets, 19 (Box 16)
- Membership information, 19 (Box 16)
- Century Farm correspondence, 19 (Box 16)
- By-laws as amended, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
- Constitution & by-laws, 19 (Box 16)
- Ag Society bibliography, 19 (Box 16)
- Historical & contributor information, 19 (Box 16)
- Journalism award, 1979 (Box 16)
- Financial records, 1975-1986 (Box 17)
- Pictures & proofs, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
- Harold Creal picture, 19 (Box 17)
- Article: "Revolution Predated by 32 Farms in State", 19 (Box 17)
- NYS Ag Society Transactions, 1856, 1892, 1898 (Box 17)